In this video, I will show you how to
turn a casual product photo like this
into a professional studio shot like
this or multiple variations or heck even
a very cool looking 360 style video of
your product. And the tool that we're
using for this is called free big
spaces. So this one is the absolute best
AI content creation platform. And the
thing here is that this tool allows you
to build these continuous workflows. So
you get faster results, more consistent
results and everything is organized in
one place. So for example, here we can
see that we could use any one of these
models for example to create this image.
So we can do Nanabanana 2, Nanabanana,
Nanabanana Pro. We have access to every
AI image and video generator editor
upscaler here in one place. So we don't
need to juggle between multiple windows
or subscriptions. And also we can say
goodbye to those chatbased editors and
generators where you always need to hope
for consistency and hope that the
conversation doesn't get lost. So this
is the new way to create content. And
now let's get started. Now if you're
completely new to free spaces, I have
actually made a separate video where I
show you how everything works. But
basically the idea is simple. So first
and foremost you have this workflow that
I have built over here. You can actually
check this workflow with my link in the
description and you can just clone it
and start to mess around with it. You
can start to generate these photos and
videos right off the bat. You don't need
to understand how this is built and you
can move nodes around. You can change
the text over here if you want to. But I
recommend following along because I will
explain to you what everything here does
so that it's more clear for you when you
start to mess around with it. Then
secondly, before I show you this
workflow, let me show you a very simple
example. So the idea in free big spaces
is that you have this kind of an
infinite canvas where you can drag and
drop nodes. For example, we can add a
text node. We can press F to zoom in on
it. And for example, we can say
something like create an image of a
shoe. And then instead of hitting send,
we're going to connect that into an
image generator node. For example, like
this. And we will connect the text into
the text port over here. And we can just
hit generate. [music]
And here is our image of a shoe. Now,
something I want to bring up is that
free spaces actually offers you
unlimited generations with Nanobanana 2
for example. So, that is the latest
state-of-the-art one of the best image
generators right now. So, if you for
example choose Nanobanana 2 over here
and we can choose either 1K or 2K
quality and you can actually see that it
says run unlimited. And obviously, you
need a paid monthly subscription to
access this model. But when you have it,
you can generate an unlimited number of
images with this best models. So that is
pretty incredible. So you can basically
test things for free. So now here is an
image we created with Nano Banana. And
this cost us zero credits, which is
awesome. And basically all the key nodes
you will ever need is this text node. As
you can see here, we can give text
inputs. Then you have image generator
nodes. And then in a very similar
fashion you have video generator nodes.
And then one more thing I want to
mention before we start to go through
the product photo workflow is this
assistant node. So this is essentially
like chachi BT. So for example, let's
type in something like create a poem of
a cat. And now we can choose the model.
For example, we can use the cha GBT1
mini model. And if I hit send, it will
generate a poem of a cat. Very similar
to how you would use Chachi PT. And
there we go. Here is a unique little
poem of a cat. And with this, you
actually understand the basics of the
platform. So now we can actually move on
to this product photo workflow. And
remember, you can access this with my
link in the description. So you don't
need to follow along if you don't want
to. And now as the first step, what I
have done here is that I have just
dragged and dropped an image of my shoe
into this view. So this is actually
something I took from this office space
the other day. This is a worn shoe, so
you can see a bit dirt in it even. But
that's not the point. The point here is
just how good the AI can do of a job
with a with a product filter like this.
So now the next step what I have done
here is that I have given it some
instructions. So, I have connected this
product image into an assistant node.
So, I'm using the GPT1 or the GPT5 model
to turn these instructions into a prompt
because I'm not that good at writing
those product advertisement prompts. So,
I'm just basically telling the AI to
detail a close-up three quarter view
product style photo of the main product
set against dark fashion studio
background and yada yada yada. And as
you can see as the result we get this
kind of a professional prompt and it's
using language and it's using a
structure that I could not produce
myself. So that is very helpful. And now
we can connect that assistant node
result we get into another image
generator. So as you can see we have
connected the text over here and then we
have also added this image of my shoe
and we have connected that with the
image part here in this image generator
node. So we are using Nanabanana 2 over
here and I have created a couple of 2K
resolution pictures. So it's not even
spending my credits. And then once
you're satisfied with it, once you get
good results with the unlimited
generations, then you can switch this
into 4K and hit run a couple of times to
get the maximum quality. But that's just
to demonstrate what is possible right
now. So I think that this image is
pretty freaking amazing. And if we check
on it, it does not look blurry or low
resolution at all. So then as the next
step based on this photo, I have created
a couple of variations. So I have
actually grouped these three image
generator nodes and called it the
variations group. But basically I have
done the exact same thing as I have done
here. So I have just added an image
generator node over here and we're once
again using Google Nana Banana 2. So
here I have told top-down view the same
scene and I have tagged main photo here
and that is actually a very cool and
easy way for you to reference to photos
from the past. So as you can see this
one is called main photo. So now if I
reference to this photo that is if I
want to use this photo in another photo
in the future here in the workflow all I
need to do is just add this add symbol
and then tag it into the conversation or
into the workflow which is absolutely
fantastic. So it makes it so easy to
follow and also the AI knows exactly
what you're talking about. But
nonetheless, top down view, same scene.
And I have created a couple of pictures.
And as you can see, a couple of these
kind of failed. I don't think that this
looks natural because the shoe is
standing on its own. So I think it's
better if it's lying on the floor like
this. So this one is a perfect photo. So
I had to try it three times. Yeah, it's
not perfect by no means. And I also
created this front view of the shoe and
then a detailed closeup of the front
part of the shoe. And this time I would
say that I want to have a video where it
starts from this scene. So we are in a
close-up view of the shoe and then we
basically spin around the shoe in a 360
style. So as the first step I enhanced
the image quality because as I said I
used the 2K resolution and also you
could have just chosen the 4K resolution
then you would have gotten the best
resolution over here. You wouldn't even
need to enhance it. But in my case,
since these are test photos and I
happened to like this one a lot, I
actually wanted to use it right off the
bat without regenerating. So I'm using
an image enhancer node. So once again,
it's something you can type in over here
into the node selector. So the image
upscaler node is something that enhances
your photos. So here's the enhanced
version of this product photo we just
generated. And then I have done once
again the assistant node number two. So,
I'm telling the AI to create an accurate
prompt for a product video with a 360
degree rotation of this product that I
have attached over here. Keep it
minimal. Don't add text or anything.
Just nice looking 360 view of the
product. And then what I have done there
is I have gotten this result from
ChachiP. And then I have connected that
instruction that is this prompt that I
got back into a video generator node
right over here. And then I have also
added this image as the starting
reference frame. So as you can see it
says start image. So basically it is
forcing the video to start from this
frame. And then basically I hit generate
and off we go. So as you can see it
starts from that frame and now this is a
wonderful looking 360 video of my
product. And as I said, you could wire
this in a such a way where you get, for
example, 50 of these photos or 10 of
those videos if you want to. And what's
really cool here is that you can just
choose, for example, over here, if you
hit run unlimited, you can either choose
to run this node only, so it will just
regenerate this photo, or you can run
from here, where it would basically
generate these three photos we did over
here. Then it would do the enhancement
and then it would do this instruction
for the video again and then it would
create the video. So you can run the
entire workflow and you can literally
generate hundreds of product photos with
just a simple click of a button. And
better yet if you're using the lower
resolution model, you can test this
without spending any credits whatsoever.
So I think that is a wonderful way for
you to create wonderful looking product
photos and advertisements from a casual
photo you can just take in your home or
office or wherever you might be. But
that said, make sure to check the
description because I have left this
workflow there so you can start to mess
around with it right off the bat. Also,
if you're interested in free spaces and
you want to commit to a paid plan, you
will actually get a 20% discount in the
description as well for the premium and
premium plus annual plans. I have also
left a link to a video where I go
through all these different node types.
So, it is essentially a full course on
how to use these workflow builders
because these are the future of AI
content creation. Now, that's it for
this one. Thank you so much for
watching. Leave your thoughts down
below. If you want to see me do
something else in free spaces, please
let me know. I hope to see you in the
next video.